scorehero.com 2019-03-07

# Score Hero - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Statement sets forth the information gathering, use, and dissemination practices of ScoreHero, its affiliate and subsidiary companies ("ScoreHero") in connection with its Web site located at www.ScoreHero.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Statement addresses ScoreHero's practices regarding information collected only directly through or from the Site - it does not address or govern any information gathering, use, or dissemination practices related to information collected from the visitor (sometimes referred to as "you" or "your") other than directly through or from the Site, including, without limitation, from or via telephone, facsimile, postal mail, personal delivery, or other or additional offline means or media. This Privacy Statement is incorporated into ScoreHero's Statement of Use by reference, as if set forth fully therein, which must be reviewed and accepted by you.

**1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**

Please be aware that the Site is a general audience web site, not directed to children under the age of 13, and must not be used by children under 13. ScoreHero and the Site take important measures to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If you are the parent of a child under the age of 13 who you believe is accessing the Site or contributing personal information wittingly or unwittingly to ScoreHero or the Site, contact ScoreHero immediately as set forth in Section 4, so that we may restrict access and destroy such information.

Subject to the foregoing, ScoreHero may collect or track (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to the Site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with ScoreHero via e-mail, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, contest entries, surveys, e-mail, and other online avenues (including, without limitation, demographic and personal profile data), and (4) aggregate and user-specific information regarding which pages Site visitors access.

ScoreHero may place Internet "cookies" on visitors' hard drives. Internet cookies save data about individual visitors, such as the visitor's name, password, user-name, shopping cart, screen preferences, and the pages of a site viewed by the visitor. When the visitor revisits the Site, ScoreHero may recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor's experience accordingly. Visitors may decline Internet cookies, if any, by using the appropriate feature of their Web client software, if available.

ScoreHero also may use Web bugs to gather, store, and track certain information related to your visit to and activity on the Site. A Web "bug" is a file object, which can be a graphic image such as a transparent one pixel-by-one pixel graphics file, which is placed on a Web page or in an e-mail message to monitor user activity. A Web bug can gather, for example, the IP address of your computer, the time the Web page was viewed, and the type of browser used.

When a visitor performs a search within the Site, ScoreHero, without limitation, may record information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed. ScoreHero may also record limited information for every search request and use that information to solve technical problems with the services available directly or indirectly in connection with the Site and to calculate overall usage statistics.

**2\. Use of Personal Data Collected**

Personal data collected by ScoreHero may be used by ScoreHero for many reasons, for example, for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, for fulfillment of a requested transaction or recordkeeping, or to customize the content and layout of the Site. Aggregate data on visitors' home servers may be used for internal purposes, and individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to ScoreHero may be added to ScoreHero's databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding Site updates, new products and services, and upcoming events.

ScoreHero also may use Site visitor data to contact the Site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement (if applicable), Privacy Statement, and any other policies or agreements relevant to Site visitors.

**3\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties**

Aggregate data on visitors' home servers and individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, may be provided to third parties such as marketing firms.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Identifiable and non-identifiable visitor information and data which visitors provide to ScoreHero may be provided to third parties who provide products, information, or services which ScoreHero believes that visitors may be interested in directly or indirectly purchasing or obtaining. Identifiable or non-identifiable data also may be disclosed or distributed to another party with which ScoreHero enters or reasonably may enter into a corporate transaction, such as, for example, a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or asset purchase, or to a third party pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, in response to a request by or on behalf of any local, state, federal, or other government agency, department, or body, whether or not pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, or if determined by ScoreHero in its sole judgment that such disclosure or distribution is appropriate to protect the life, health, or property of ScoreHero or any other person or entity.

While ScoreHero may undertake efforts to see that any third party to which ScoreHero shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data is under a contractual obligation to use the personal data solely for the purposes for which the data was disclosed, such third parties are independent third parties over which ScoreHero exercises no control. ScoreHero is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices.

This Site may contain links to other World Wide Web sites or advertisements for or placed by third parties. ScoreHero is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites, advertisers, or third parties, or for the content of such sites or advertisements. It is possible that these links or advertisements, themselves, may be used by third parties or others to collect personal or other information about Site visitors. It is solely the visitor's obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other Web sites and of these advertisers and third parties.

**4\. Security Measures and Communicating with ScoreHero**

ScoreHero has implemented numerous security features that are designed to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. For example, ScoreHero undertakes all efforts to maintain a secure server; does not store any user credit card information; and requires certain employees and service providers who work for or with ScoreHero to sign confidentiality agreements restricting their use of any data related to user information. However, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from ScoreHero via this Site or e-mail cannot be and is not guaranteed. Accordingly, ScoreHero is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet.

**5\. Comments, Notices and Chat Rooms**

Comments posted to any of our Web pages are public. With respect to chat rooms, ScoreHero does not, and is not obligated to, monitor or review any areas on the Site, or the content therein, where users transmit or post communications or communicate with each other regarding ScoreHero or content on the Site, including but not limited to, communications in chat rooms, bulletin boards or other user forums. Please refer to Section 1 of the Statement of Use for further detail concerning Materials Submitted to the Site. As such, ScoreHero assumes no liability for the accuracy of such information, no duty to update or correct such information, and no liability for such communications arising under the laws of copyright, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise.

**6\. Opt-Out Right**

Except as necessary for ScoreHero to provide the services, information, or products requested by a visitor, the visitor may opt out of having his or her personally identifiable information, which has been voluntarily provided to ScoreHero through online forms, registration forms, contest entries, surveys, e-mail, or another online avenue, prospectively retained by ScoreHero, used by ScoreHero for secondary purposes, or disclosed by ScoreHero to third parties, by contacting ScoreHero via e-mail at contact@scorehero.com. (This does not apply to collection of the type of Web browser of the visitor to the Site or to information provided or collected that does not meet the description in this Section 6.)

**7\. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data**

Upon a visitor's request via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone, ScoreHero will provide to the visitor a summary of any personally identifiable information retained by ScoreHero regarding the visitor that has been voluntarily provided by the visitor to ScoreHero through online forms, registration forms, contest entries, surveys, e-mail, or another online avenue. A visitor may modify, correct, change or update his or her personally identifiable information by contacting ScoreHero via e-mail at the addresses above.

**8\. Right to Change Privacy Statement**

ScoreHero may change this Privacy Statement at any time. Notice of any new or revised Privacy Statement, as well as the location of the new or revised statement, will be posted on the Site for at least 60 days after the change. It is the obligation of users returning to the Site to learn of changes to the Privacy Statement since their last visit. Any change to this Privacy Statement shall be effective as to any visitor who has visited the Site before the change was made.

**This Privacy Policy is updated as of January 25, 2010.**
